Guide to the Rice University Past Faculty and Staff records, 1961-1996 UA 008
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Past Faculty and Staff A-Z, 1915-2003, 119315
  - Tate, Joseph A. - Fine Arts, 1970-1973; 169450 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Tate, MAJ William A. - Naval Science, [?]-1967; 169451 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Taylor, Harwood - Architecture, 1961; 169453 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Taylor, John Alfred - English, 1962-1964; 169452 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Taylor, Michael E. - Mathematics, 1976-1982; 169455 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Taylor, LT Nelson D. - Naval Science, 1965-[?]; 169456 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Tarr, Jim - Chemical Engineering, 1978, 1980; 169458 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Terzis, George N. - Philosophy, 1980; 169459 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Thames, Howard D., Jr. - Mathematical Sciences, 1975-1993 [?]; 169460 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Thibodeaux, Murphy H. - Civil Engineering, 1949-1966; 169461 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Thirsk, Wayne R. - Economics, 1972-1974, 1976-1977; 169462 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Thomas, Arthur L. - Accounting, 1977-1980; 169463 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Thomas, Richard Ludlow - Business Administration, 1962-1963; 169464 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Thompson, William J. - Civil Engineering, 1964-1965; 169465 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Thomsen, Charles B. - Architecture, 1973-1982; 169466 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Thomson, Bruce M. - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1976-1978; 169467 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Threadgold, Lawrence T. - Biology, 1967-1968; 169468 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Tierney, Myles - Mathematics, 1965-1967; 169469 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Tobias, Paul - Psychology, 1972-1975; 169470 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Tobocman, William - Physics, 1958-1962; 169500 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Trail, LT George A. - Naval Science, 1963 [?]; 169501 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Triandafilidis, George E. - Civil Engineering, 1961-1964; 169503 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Trocme, Etienne - Religious Studies, 1979-1980; 169505 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Troelstra, Arne - Electrical Engineering, 1969-1980; 169507 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Trost, Rudolph F. - Bioengineering, 1974-1975; 169509 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Tsanoff, Radoslav Andrea - Philosophy, 1915-1956, 1961-1973; 169510 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Tullock, Gordon - Economics and Political Science, 1967-1968; 169511 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Twiford, Linda Kay - French, 1978-1980; 169512 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Ugi, Ivar Karl - Chemistry, 1973-1974; 169513 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Umstattd, James G. - Education, 1965; 169520 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Underwood, John R. - Mathematics, 1973-1974; 169523 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Ushinsky, Constantin D. - Russian, 1973-1980; 169524 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Uzzell, John D. - Anthropology, 1971-1979; 169525 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Valdivieso, Mercedes V. - Spanish, 1968-1989; 169528 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Valentine, Jerome Lynn - Accounting, 1976-1981; 169530 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Vallbona, Rima R. - Spanish/Portuguese/Classics, 1981-1983; 169533 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - van Lohuizen, Jan Reint - Political Science, 1981-1982; 169535 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Veltman, James - Architecture, 1973-1978; 169536 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Venable, James R. - Chemical Engineering, 1979-1981; 169537 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Vendler, Zeno - Philosophy, 1973-1974; 169538 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Vermeulen, Peter James - Mechanical Engineering, 1960-1964; 169539 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Victory, Sidney Patrick - Civil Engineering, 1963-1965; 169540 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Vincent, Gilbert - Religious Studies, 1981; 169541 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Vorhaben, Jean Ellen - Biology, 1979-1981; 169542 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Wadsworth, Philip A. - French/Dean of Humanities, 1964-1973; 169614 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Wagner, Charles D. - Chemistry, 1974-1976; 169615 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Wagner, Terry J. - Electrical Engineering, 1977-1978; 169616 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Walker, Mary Beth - Economics, 1982; 169617 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Wall, Frederick - Chemistry, 1972-1978; 169618 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Wang, Hai-Li - Mathematical Sciences, 1982; 169619 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Wann, Trenton William - Psychology, 1950-1979; 169620 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Warme, John E. - Geology, 1967-1982; 169621 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Warner, Jeffrey Lee - Geology, 1981-1982; 169622 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Warren, David B. - Fine Arts, 1967-1973; 169623 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Waters, James Stephen - Electrical Engineering, 1920-1964; 169624 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Waters, Kenneth H. - Geology, 1982-1983; 169625 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Webster, Sidney M. - Mathematics, 1981-1982; 169626 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Wegner, Robert Carl - Geology, 1981-1982; 169627 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Weidler, Jay B., Jr. - Civil Engineering, 1961-1965; 169628 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Weinstein, Alan David - Mathematics, 1978-1979; 169629 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Weiss, Kenneth M. - Anthropology, 1980-1982; 169630 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Welch, Ashley James - Electrical Engineering, 1960-1963; 169631 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Welsh, Hugh C. - Medical Advisor to the Board, 1964-1965; 169632 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Wendt, COL James R., Jr. - Military Science, 1967-1969 [?]; 169633 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Wendt, Richard E., III - Electrical Engineering, 1983; 169634 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Wenkert, Ernest - Chemistry, 1973-1980; 169635 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Westheimer, Alan D. - Jones School of Administration, 1982; 169636 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Weston, Arthur - Health and Physical Education, 1952-1964; 169637 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Whale, John Seldon - Religion, 1962; 169638 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Wheatley, Katherine Ernestine - French, 1964; 169639 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Wheeler, Wayne - Sociology, 1965-1967; 169640 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - White, Kenneth J. - Economics, 1972-1981; 169641 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - White, Robert H. - Biochemistry, 1976-1979; 169642 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Wiederhold, Alan D. - Mathematics, 1975-1976, 1979; 169643 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Wieting, David Warren - Biomedical Engineering, 1970-1974; 169644 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Wilbratte, Barry J. - Ecomonics, 1980; 169645 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Wilby, COL Langfitt B. - Military Science, 1962-[?]; 169646 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Wildenthal, Bryan Hobson - Physics, 1964-1966; 169647 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Wilder, Amos Niven - Religion, 1963; 169648 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Wilkins, Burleigh Taylor - Philosophy, 1965-1967; 169649 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Willems, Edwin Paul - Psychology, 1965-1968; 169650 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Willems, Edward Paul - Architecture, 1975-1979; 169651 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Williams, Edward B. - Mathematics, 1972-1975; 169652 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Williams, George Guion - English, 1923-1968; 169653 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Williams, James L. - Jones School of Administration, 1977-1980; 169654 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Williams, Kathleen - English, 1966-1967; 169655 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Wilson, Harold Albert - Physics, 1916-1964; 169656 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Wilson, James Lee - Geology, 1965; 169657 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Wilson, Joy C. - English, 1967-1968; 169658 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Wilson, Marsha A. - Jones School of Administration, 1980-1981; 169659 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Winch, Donald N. - Economics, 1965; 169660 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Wingfield, Magruder B. - Architecture, 1965-1966; 169661 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Winkelman, Henry T. - Architecture, 1974-1978; 169662 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Wirz, Dadi - Art and Art History, 1973-1980; 169663 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Witherington, Paul - English, 1964-1965; 169664 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Wodtke, Friedrich Wilhelm - German, 1963-1964; 169665 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Wojecki, Edward J. - Physical Education/Trainer/Physical Therapy, 1947-1967; 169666 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Wong, Pit-Mann - Mathematics, 1977-1978; 169667 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Wood, Donald Ira - Education, 1961-1983; 169668 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Wood, R. Jerome - Architecture, 1976-1977; 169669 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Woodward, Val W. - Biology, 1961-1967; 169670 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Worzel, J. Lamar - Geology, 1974-1979; 169671 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Wright, Marcus W. - Mathematics, 1974-1976; 169672 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Wright, Neil R. - Economics, 1972-1980; 169673 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Wright, Qunicy J. - International Relations, 1966; 169674 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Yang, Paul Chien-Ping - Architecture, 1974-1976; 169675 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Yates, Jacques Frank - Psychology, 1973; 169676 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Young, Al - English, 1982; 169677 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Young, William John Shik [Yuen] - Physics, 1967-1968; 169678 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Young, William N., III - Civil Engineering, 1984; 169679 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Zalta, Edward N. - Philosophy, 1981-1982; 169680 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Zanartu, Enrique - Art and Art History, 1979-1980; 169681 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Zuidweg, Johan Karel - Electrical Engineering, 1961-1962; 169682 (Box 11, Folder 69)
- Series II: Past Faculty and Staff A-Z, 1953-2014, 169683
  The following files have incomplete information. It is hard to determine the exact working dates for all of the faculty listed. There are also a few files that do not focus on a single faculty member, but instead groups of faculty.
  - Adams, John T. - Chemistry, 1973-1974; 169684 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Appointment Recommendations for the Academic Affairs Committee, 1975; 169685 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Bean, Richard N. - Economics, 1975; 169686 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Begley, Wayne E. - Fine Arts, 1974-1975, 1985; 169687 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Beloff, Beth - Architecture, 1976-1977; 169688 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Bird, Graham H. - Philosophy, 1975; 169689 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Bower, Gary Richard - Philosophy, 1974-1975; 169690 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Butler, Murdock M. - Chemistry, 1973; 169691 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Chapman, David - Architecture, 1976-1977, 1981-1983 [?]; 169692 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Cochran, Alice C. - Religious Studies, 1974-1975; 169693 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Clement-Cormier, Yvonne C. - Biology, 1975; 169694 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Cox, Douglas - Fine Arts, 1975-1977 [?]; 169695 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Cox, Richard D. - Fine Arts, 1975-1976; 169696 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Cronin, Robin - Fine Arts, 1976; 169697 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Duperray, Brigitte - French, 1975; 169698 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Entzminger, Robert L. - English, 1975-1976; 169699 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Estevez, Victor A. - Classics, 1974-1975; 169700 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Evans, Benny Dan - Mathematics, 1976; 169701 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Gibilaro, Lorenzo Giovanni - Chemical Engineering, 1977; 169702 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Grimes, Richard M. - Accounting, 1974; 169703 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Guertin, Ralph F. - Physics, 1970-1976; 169704 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Hanley, Paul J. - Economics, 1974-1975; 169705 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Harrison, Michael F. A. - Physics, 1974; 169706 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Head, Thomas James - Mathematical Sciences, 1975-1976; 169707 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Houston, M. H., Jr. - Geology, 1975-1977; 169708 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Iliffe, John K. - Computer Science, 1975; 169709 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Johnson, Cynthia June - French, 1976-1977; 169710 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Johnson, Michael Truitt - Political Science, 1977; 169711 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Johnson, Nancy Kay Leavenworth - Accounting, 1975; 169712 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Kacen, Alex - Education, 1974; 169713 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Kappel, Andrew J. - English, 1975-1976; 169714 (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Kendall, Richard Parker - Mathematical Sciences, 1975-1976, 1981-1982 [?]; 169715 (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - Klein, Robert Allen - Economics, 1975; 169716 (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - Linville, Jack, Jr. - Architecture, 1976-1979 [?]; 169717 (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - Lohse, Margie C. - Anthropology, 1974-1975, 1977; 169718 (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - Ludman, Earl A. - Philosophy, 1974-1975; 169719 (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - Marsh, Mary E. - Chemistry, 1975; 169720 (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - Maryland, Edward J., Jr. - Mathematics, 1976-1977; 169721 (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Matalon, Marlene - Fine Arts, 1976; 169722 (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Mayur, Neela - Mathematics, 1974; 169723 (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - McDonald, James J. - Architecture, 1975-1976; 169724 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Mitchell, William E. - Art and Art History, 1977; 169726 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Mladenka, Kenneth R. - Political Science, 1974-1975; 169727 (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Myers, John Robert - Mathematics, 1976-1978 [?]; 169728 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Naval Science Faculty - Additions and Deletions, 1975; 169729 (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - Norris, Mary - Shepherd School of Music, 1976-1980 [?]; 169730 (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - Parsons, David G. - Fine Arts, 1953-1981; 169731 (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - Pintard, René - French, 1973-1975; 169732 (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - Reasoner, Harry M. - Political Science, 1976; 169733 (Box 11, Folder 118)
  - Refaey, Kamal M. A. - Chemistry, 1975-1976; 169734 (Box 11, Folder 119)
  - Reingold, Maxine Frosch - French and Italian, 1974-1975; 169735 (Box 11, Folder 120)
  - Resignations, 1971, 1973-1976; 169736 (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - Roberts, David L. - Economics, 1975; 169737 (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - Saalman, Howard - Mellon Professor in Humanities, 1977; 169738 (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - Sanborn, Hugh - Religious Studies, 1974-1981 [?]; 169739 (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - Scott, David Warren - Mathematical Sciences, 1976-2014; 169740 (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - Seitz, William A. - Chemistry, 1975-1976; 169862 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Smereka, Myroslaw - Economics, 1974-1975; 169863 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Soll, Dieter G. - Biochemistry, 1977; 169864 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Sposato, Donna Mary - French and Italian, 1976-1977; 169865 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Stewart, J. Michael - Electrical Engineering, 1976; 169866 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Szyfman, Tatiana P. - German and Russian, 1975; 169867 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Thomas, Robert W., Jr. - Economics, 1976; 169868 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Tuggle, Francis D. - Administration, 1977; 169869 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Whitehead, Glen R. - Fine Arts, 1976-1977; 169870 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Whitehead, Lawrence W. - Architecture, 1974; 169871 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Whiteside, Ruth Ann - History, 1976-1977; 169872 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Winograd, Garry - Fine Arts, 1976; 169873 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Woodgate, Sheila D. - Chemistry, 1976-1977; 169874 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Series III: Past Staff and Personnel (Post-Docs, Researchers, Non-Academic), 1950-1975, 119385
  The following files except for the first are organized by alphabet. Each letter contains two groups of files: one for staff and administration and the other for fellows and research associates. The dates on each file correspond to the date of the materials within the files. The exact working dates of the individuals are unknown. While there are some coaches files in Series I, there also some located in this series.
  - Appointments and personnel changes, 1962-1964; 169875 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - A, 1962-1970; 169876 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - B (1 of 2), 1963-1973; 169877 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - B (2 of 2), 1963-1973; 169878 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - C, 1962-1974; 169879 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - D, 1961-1971; 169880 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - E, 1963-1970; 169881 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - F, 1963-1971; 169882 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - G, 1950-1971; 169883 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - H, 1962-1971; 169884 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - I, 1969-1971; 169885 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - J, 1962-1970; 169886 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - K, 1962-1971; 169887 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - L, 1963-1971; 169888 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - M (photograph) (1 of 2), 1962-1975; 169889 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - M (2 of 2), 1962-1975; 169890 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - N, 1963-1970; 169891 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - O, 1962-1971; 169892 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - P, 1962-1971; 169893 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - R, 1963-1971; 169894 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - S (1 of 2), 1962-1971; 169895 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - S (2 of 2), 1962-1971; 169896 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - T, 1953-1970; 169897 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - U, 1967; 169898 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - V, 1967-1971; 169899 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - W, 1963-1971; 169900 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Y, 1962-1971; 169901 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Z, 1965-1971; 169902 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Series IV: Past Faculty and Staff A-Z, 1947-1991, 119386
  - Berndt, Jerry L. - Athletic Director and Head Football Coach, 1986-1988; 169903 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Brady, David William - Political Science, 1974-1987; 169904 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Breedin, Brent - Director of Information Services, 1981-1986; 169905 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Class, Calvin M. - Physics, 1952-1985; 169906 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Curtis, Morton L. - Mathematics, 1964-1989; 169907 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Erfurth, August - Executive Athletic Director, 1960-1986; 169908 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Evans, Dale William - Human Performance, 1981-1988; 169909 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Evans, Elinor - Architecture, 1964-1986; 169910 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Francis, Myrtle - Health and Physical Education, 1972-1975; 169911 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Franklin, Joseph L. - Chemistry, 1963-1978; 169912 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Garside, Charles, Jr. - History, 1966-1987; 169913 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Guilmartin, John F. - History, 1983-1987; 169914 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Hudson, Jackie Lee - Health and Physical Education, 1980-1987; 169915 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Jones, Robert B. - English, 1981-1987; 169916 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Kapusta, Sergio - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1981-1991; 169917 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Kennon, Paul A. - Architecture (photograph in portforlio), 1964-1990; 169919 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Kilpatrick, John E. - Chemistry, 1947-1985; 169920 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Konrad, Linn B. - French and Italian, 1980-1989; 169918 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Kung, Hans - Mellon Distinguished Visiting Professor, 1987, 1989; 169921 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Kurtzman, Jeffrey G. - Shepherd School of Music, 1975-1987; 169922 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Leland, Thomas W. - Chemical Engineering, 1954-1986; 169923 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Livingston, Larry J. - Shepherd School of Music, 1981-1986; 169924 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Lutes, Loren - Civil Engineering, 1967-1987; 169925 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Martin, Joseph P. - Biology, 1981-1988; 169926 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Montgomery, Stephen N. - Architecture/Administrative Science, 1975-1979, 1984; 169927 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Moore, Walter P., Jr. - Civil Engineering/Architecture, 1975-1984; 169928 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Morehead, James C., Jr. - Architecture/Registrar, 1940-1979; 169929 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Parsons, David G. - Art and Art History, 1953-1981; 169930 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Penrose, Roger - Mathematics, 1983-1987; 169931 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Phillips, Gerry C. - Physics, 1949-1988; 169932 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Ransom, Harry S., Jr. - Architecture, 1956-1981; 169933 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Rath, R. John - History, 1963-1983; 169934 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Reich, Peter A. - Linguistics, 1986-1987; 169935 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Rhodes, Harold R. - Director of Safety and Security, 1966-1989; 169936 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Rimlinger, Gaston C. - Economics, 1960-1988; 169937 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Risser, Jack R. - Physics, 1946-1981; 169938 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Roberts, John Melville - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1959-1989; 169951 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Scheer, Stephen - Photography, 1984; 169952 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Schum, David A. - Psychology, 1966-1985; 169953 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Sherman, Jerome N. - Religious Studies, 1973-1983; 169954 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Spears, Monroe K. - English, 1964-1986; 169955 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Storck, Roger - Biology, 1966-1985; 169956 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Stout, Janis P. - English, 1977-1987; 169957 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Sullivan, Michael - Naval Science, 1986-1989; 169958 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Thrall, Robert M. - Mathematical Sciences/Administrative Science, 1968-1984; 169959 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Walker, William F. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1965-1988; 169960 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Ward, Joseph A. - English, 1964-1989; 169961 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Wierum, Frederic A. - Mechanical Engineering/Dean of Students, 1961-1989; 169962 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Wilhoit, James C., Jr. - Mechanical Engineering, 1954-1981; 169963 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Williams, Donald L. - Architecture, 1973-1985; 169964 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Zirilli, Francesco - Mathematical Sciences, 1980-1988; 169965 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Series V: Past Faculty and Staff A-Z, 1949-1992, 119387
  - Abrahams, Julia - Electrical Engineering, 1979-1983; 169966 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Adair, Linda - Anthropology, 1980-1988; 169967 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Adams, John A. S. - Geochemistry, 1954-1988; 169968 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Adams, Raymond A. - Religious Studies, 1981; 169969 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Alborn, Ray - Head Football Coach, 1981-1983; 169970 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Allen, Catherine - Shepherd School of Music, 1983-1984; 169971 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Allen, Robert H. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1988; 169972 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Alperin, Roger C. - Mathematics, 1982-1983; 169973 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Anderson, Craig A. - Psychology, 1980-1988; 169974 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Anderson, James August - Philosophy, 1986-1987; 169975 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Anderson, James E. - Political Science, 1978-1986; 169976 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Andrews, Dwight Douglas - Art and Art History, 1986-1988; 169977 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Asare, Benjamin - Sociology, 1988-1989; 169978 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Awapara, Jorge - Biochemistry, 1956-1984; 169979 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Bäck, Allan T. - Philosophy, 1983-1984; 169980 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Bacon, Thomas - Shepherd School of Music, 1977-1984; 169981 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Bailey, Toby N. - Mathematics, 1985-1986; 169982 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Baker, Donald R. - Geology, 1966-1988; 169983 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Bannerot, Richard B. - Mechanical Engineering, 1987; 169984 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Barker, J. R. - Health and Physical Education, 1950-1986; 169985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Barlow, Grant H. - Biomedical Engineering Laboratory, 1986-1988; 169986 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Barndollar, Robert B. - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1983-1986; 169987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Barnhill, J. Allen - Shepherd School of Music, 1981-1984; 169988 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Bartle, Andrew B. - Architecture, 1985-1987; 169989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Baxter, Trevor - English, 1985; 169990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Beaman, Darlene S. - English, 1985; 169991 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Beattie, Ann - English, 1986; 169992 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Begley, Wayne E. - Art and Art History, 1985; 169993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Belval, Thomas - Chemical Engineering, 1984; 169994 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Benedek, Laslo - Mellon Professor in Humanities, 1985; 169995 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Ben-Horim, Moshe - Administration, 1985-1986; 169996 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Benjamin, Robert C. A. - Administrative Science, 1985-1988; 169997 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Benrath, Gustav Adolf - Religious Studies, 1987; 169998 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Benson, John L. - Space Physics and Astronomy, 1983-1986; 169999 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Berget, Susan M. - Biochemistry, 1978-1989; 170000 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Betz, Otto - Religious Studies, 1985-1986; 170001 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Biesele, Marguerite A. - Anthropology, 1981, 1984-1988; 170002 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Billars, Stephen Louis - Administrative Science, 1984-1986; 170003 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Birdwell, Al E. - Administrative Science, 1986-1988; 170004 (Box 15, Folder 20)